rightside.co 2018-02-05

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated: April 30, 2017
Version 2.0
THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME
(“POLICY”), GOVERNS THE INFORMATION RIGHTSIDE GROUP,
LTD. (“WE,” “US,” OR “OUR”) COLLECTS ABOUT YOU WHEN YOU
ACCESS THIS WEBSITE (the “SITE”). THIS POLICY ALSO
PROVIDES NOTICE OF CERTAIN INFORMATION THAT RIGHTSIDE
MAY COLLECT OR RECEIVE FROM ITS AFFILIATES IN THE COURSE
OF ITS BUSINESS OPERATIONS. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS
POLICY, DO NOT USE THE SITE.
THIS POLICY IS PART OF AND INCORPORATED INTO THE
SITE TERMS OF USE (the “TERMS”). BY PROVIDING PERSONAL
INFORMATION OR OTHER INFORMATION TO US OR BY USING
OUR SITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE PRACTICES
DESCRIBED IN THE POLICY.
1. INFORMATION YOU GIVE US
We collect any information you enter on the Site or give us in any
other way (such as through an email, survey, or letter). Such
information may include your name, postal and email address, and
phone and facsimile numbers, but can vary depending upon how
you use our Site.
2. INFORMATION COLLECTION
A. Cookies. Like many websites, we use “cookies“. Cookies are
alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard
drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to
recognize your browser. We use persistent, identifying cookies to
remember your information and to link your activities to you. While
you can take steps to warn off, block or disable cookies, if you do,

the Site may not function and appear as we have designed it.
Nonetheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by
following the instructions associated with your browser. Our cookies
collect information such as:
i. the domain name and host from which you access the Internet
and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to
ours;
ii. the date and time you access the Site and pages you visit;
iii. your computer’s IP address and information about its operating
system, platform and the Web browser type and version you use;
iv. demographic and other non-personally identifiable profile
information about you; and
v. information to combat fraud or misuse.
B. Pixel Tags. If we email you, our emails may use “pixel tags” to
determine if your email software or site can display html-formatted
email (this helps us optimize the size of our email messages and
conserve bandwidth).
C. Collection of Information by Third Parties. We use a number of
third-party widgets / applications as part of our website. These
have various functions from monitoring user activity data to linking
to a map of our Dublin office location. Each of the suppliers of
these widgets may set cookies to track the use of their widgets and
provide the best user experience associated with the widgets’
functionality. The information collected by third party cookies is
subject to the privacy policy of the third party, not this Policy.
D. Affiliates. We are the parent company of the Rightside Group,
Ltd. family of companies (the “Family of Companies”). The Family
of Companies includes the following U.S. based companies: Acquire
This Name, Inc.; DomainSite, Inc.; Hot Media, Inc.; Mobile Name
Services Incorporated; Name.com, Inc.; Name.net, Inc.; Name104,
Inc.; Name105, Inc.; Name106, Inc.; Name107, Inc.; Name108,
Inc.; Name109, Inc.; Name110, Inc.; Name111, Inc.; Name112,
Inc.; Name113, Inc.; Name114, Inc.; Name115, Inc.; Name116,
Inc.; Name117, Inc.; Name118, Inc.; Name119, Inc.; Name120,
Inc.; Rightside Group, Ltd.; Rightside Operating Co.; Secure

Business Services, Inc.; Sipence, Incorporated; Vedacore.com, Inc.;
and Whois Privacy Protection Services, Inc. The Family of
Companies also includes the following non-U.S. based companies:
Bejing United TLD Tech Co., Ltd.; DMIH Limited; Rightside Australia
Pty Ltd; Rightside Canada, Inc.; Rightside Domains Europe Limited;
and United TLD Holdco Ltd. We may receive certain personal
information from members of the Family of Companies collected by
such members, including pursuant to their privacy policies. Without
limiting the generality of the foregoing, we may receive the
following personal information:
i. In order to carry out registrant requests for registration and/or
reservation of a domain name with our affiliate, United TLD Holdco
Ltd t/a Rightside Registry (“Rightside Registry”), or sign up to
receive any services offered by Rightside Registry, individual
approved registrars (acting as data controllers) shall provide
Rightside Registry with certain information which may constitute
personal information. Such information may be shared with us. Any
personal information so received and/or collected by us, shall be
limited, in both type and use, to only that data which is required in
the fulfilment of Rightside Registry’s agreements with the Internet
Corporation of Names and Numbers (“ICANN"), the organization
that assumes responsibility for the domain name allocation. Without
commenting as to whether or not such information is considered
personal information, such collected information includes full name,
mailing address, phone number, email address, technical and
administrative contacts (if different), expiration date, and DNS
server name and IP address.
It should be noted in particular that all such information shall, as is
required by ICANN, be made available to the public via an
interactive webpage and a "port 43" WHOIS service. For the
purposes of this Policy we will refer to this information as "WHOIS
Information." Please note that we are not able to control how
members of the public may use the WHOIS Information. Such
information may include: full name, mailing address, phone
number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile
number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your

domain name registration and the name server information
associated with your domain name.
In addition, if a company is applying to become a Rightside
Registry-accredited registrar, Rightside Registry collects additional
data via the Registrar Sign-Up Portal. Such information may be
shared with us. Rightside Registry may supplement the personal
information provided with demographic data from third parties.
ii. Personal information collected by (i) Name.com, Inc. and its
affiliated registrars in accordance with the privacy policy located
at https://www.name.com/privacy-policy; (ii) Acquire This Name,
Inc. in accordance with the privacy policy located
at http://acquirethisname.com/; and (iii) Hot Media, Inc. in
accordance with the privacy policy located
at https://www.hotkeys.com/m/legal/privacy-policy.aspx;
3. OUR USE AND RETENTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
A. Use of Personal Information. We use personal information that
you submit to us for such purposes as responding to your requests;
monitoring and providing the Site; enforcing our rights and the
rights of third parties; and investigating and ensuring compliance
with the Terms.
B. Use of Other Information. We use other information about our
users for purposes such as measuring the number of visitors to
sections of our Site, making the Site more useful to visitors and
delivering targeted advertising and non-advertising content. We use
IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s
movement, and gather broad demographic information for
aggregate, non-personally identifiable use.
C. Retention of Information. We retain information for as long as
required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake
retention obligations. We may dispose of information in our
discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically
requires the handling or retention of information.

4. OUR SHARING OF INFORMATION
We share information with third parties, but only as described in
this Section 4. We may be subject to liability in cases of onward
transfer to third parties that do not conform with this Policy.
A. Advertisers and Others. We share non-personally identifiable
information with advertisers, site providers, and other persons with
whom we conduct business. Conversely, these advertisers, site
providers, and other persons may share with us information about
you that they have independently developed or acquired.
B. Site Third Parties. We contract with affiliated and non-affiliated
third parties to provide sites to us or to you on our behalf.
Examples include providing marketing assistance and analyzing
data. These third parties have access to personal information
needed to perform their functions.
C. Business Transfer. As we develop our business, we might sell or
buy businesses or their assets, or engage in acquisitions, mergers,
restructurings, changes of control, or similar transactions. In such
transactions, customer information generally is one of the
transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event of a
bankruptcy, customer information may be transferred to a
bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a
subsequent purchaser.
D. Affiliates. We may share information we have about you with
members of the Family of Companies. Each U.S. based member of
the Family of Companies adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles
(as discussed below).
E. Compliance and Safety. We may release user information when
we believe release is appropriate to:
i. comply with applicable law to respond to subpoenas, search
warrants, court orders, or legal process by public authorities,
including disclosures required by national security or law
enforcement agencies, and to respond to or otherwise address

written complaints of copyright infringement;
ii. make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential
crimes or investigate persons;
iii. enforce or apply agreements, including the Terms; or
iv. protect the rights, property, or safety of the Site, our users, or
others, including exchanging information with other companies for
fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
5. INFORMATION SECURITY
A. Your Obligations. You must protect against unauthorized access
to your personal information and to your computer. YOU MUST DO
WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.
B. Our Security Measures. We have physical, electronic, and
managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized
access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information.
HOWEVER, WE DO NOT GUARANTEE SECURITY. Neither people
nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems.
6. LINKS
The Site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for
the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be
aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements
of every web site that collects your personally identifiable
information. This Policy applies only to information collected by the
Site.
7. CHOICE
By sending us your email or other contact information, you consent
to us sending you customary business communications. You may

opt out of receiving such customary business communications by
sending such a request to legalnotice@rightside.co.
8. CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES, AND REVISIONS
A. Privacy Concerns. Your use of the Site and any dispute over
privacy is subject to the Terms. If you have any concern about
privacy at Rightside Group, Ltd., please send us a thorough
description to legalnotice@rightside.co, and we will try to resolve it.
If you think we are in default of the Terms, you may contact us at
Our Legal Notices Address in Section 9 below.
B. Notice Required by Law. In those jurisdictions that permit email
notice, if we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of
certain security systems, we will do so by email to the most current
email address provided by you to us.
C. Identity Theft. If you believe that you are a victim of identity
theft entitled by law to request information from us, write us at our
Legal Notice address (see Section 9) and we will let you know what
additional information you must provide to us. After we have
received that information, we will supply without charge the
information legally required to be disclosed that we then have,
subject to applicable law and reserving all of our rights and
defenses.
9. CONTACT INFORMATION AND INFORMATION ABOUT
ENFORCEMENT OF OUR POLICY.
For customer site matters (including questions relating to this
Policy), you may email us at legalnotice@rightside.co. To send us a
legal notice, mail it by certified mail (return receipt requested) to:
Rightside Group, Ltd., 5808 Lake Washington Blvd. Suite 300,
Kirkland, WA 98033, Attn: Legal Department.

  10. FOR EUROPEAN UNION & SWISS CITIZENS
  Privacy Shield Frameworks
• We comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the
  Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US
  Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and
  retention of personal information from European Union member
  countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the
  Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for
  Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation,
  Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any
  conflict between the policies in this Policy and the Privacy Shield
  Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more
  about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification
  page, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
• Note that you have the right to access, correct, or delete your
  personal data processed by us. For assistance with accessing,
  correcting, or deleting your personal data, please contact us
  at legalnotice@rightside.co. Please be aware that deleting your
  personal data may result in termination of the services you receive
  through us.
• In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, We commit to
  resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of
  your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals
  with inquiries or complaints regarding this Policy should first
  contact our Legal Department at legalnotice@rightside.co, or by
  certified mail (return receipt requested) at: Rightside Group, Ltd.,
  Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300,
  Kirkland, WA 98033 USA
• We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints
  under the Privacy Shield Principles to BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a
  non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the
  United States and operated by the Council of Better Business
  Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your
  complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed,

please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for
more information and to file a complaint. In addition, it is possible,
under certain limited conditions, for individuals to invoke binding
arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the US
Department of Commerce and the European Commission. Note that
the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has enforcement authority
over our compliance with this Policy.
